Historical Audiovisual Collection, 1912-2012 (bulk 1945-1996 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 6: Public Talks, 1945-2010; 693 items
  - Addresses/Debates, 1945-2010; 583 items
    - Public Lectures -- Stanley Bergen -- Medical school: who gets in and why, 1977; 535; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 77)
    - Public Lectures -- Theodore Cooper -- The making of U.S. health policy, 1977; 544; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 77)
    - Public Lectures -- Rene Dubos -- New frontiers of American society, 1977; 546; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 77)
    - Public Lectures -- Harrison Fraker -- Architecture vs. energy conscious design, 1977; 550; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 78)
    - Public Lectures -- Jean Gotmann -- Urbanization and employment -- a megalopolis, 1977; 556; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 78)
    - Syukuro Manabe - Man's impact on global climate--climatic effect of future fossil fuel combustion, 1978; 317; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 64)
    - Nani A. Palkhivala - New potential of Indo-U.S. relations, 1978; 320; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 64)
    - David Premack - Intelligence in ape and man, 1978; 321; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 64)
    - Solomon Snyder - Pain and Pleasure, 1978; 328; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 65)
    - Thomas Wright - Legalism vs. Paternalism - how new pressures are changing American universities, 1978; 337; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 65)
    - Gauss Seminar - Victor Erlich I, 1978; 465; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 75)
    - Gauss Seminar - Victor Erlich II, 1978; 466; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 76)
    - Gauss Seminar - Victor Erlich III, 1978; 467; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 76)
    - Gauss Seminar - Jacques Roger I, 1978; 468; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 76)
    - Gauss Seminar - Jacques Roger II, 1978; 469; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 76)
    - Gauss Seminar - Jacques Roger III, 1978; 470; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 76)
    - Gauss Seminar - Edward Shils I, 1978; 471; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 76)
    - Gauss Seminar - Edward Shils II, 1978; 472; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 76)
    - Gauss Seminar - Edward Shils III, 1978; 473; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 76)
    - Public Lectures -- Dean Robert Jahn - Psychic process, energy transfer, and things that go bump in the night, 1978; 558; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 78)
      Faculty Committee on Public Lectures, J. Edward Farnum Lecture. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
    - Public Lectures -- David R. Brower -- Progress as if survival mattered, 1979; 541; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 77)
    - Public Lectures -- Margaret Jay -- The British National Health System: the first 30 years, 1979; 560; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 79)
    - Public Lectures -- Kenneth E. Boulding -- Can Capitalism Survive?, 1979; 561; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 103)
      L.C. Vanuxem Lecture. Compact cassette.
    - Public Lectures -- Kenneth J. Arrow -- The Interactions Between Insurance and Equity, 1979; 562; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 103)
      Walter E. Edge Lecture. Compact cassette.
    - Fusion: Energy's Space Program (Slaner Foundation) -- Princeton Plasma Physics Laboratory, 1981; AR.2006.037; 2105; 1 Disc(s) (Box 209)
      DVD; Duration: 27 min.
    - Thirteen - Why in the World? The Middle East - Guest: Carl Brown, 1983; AR.2001.063; 1333; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 5)
    - Raphael Symposium, 1983; 1678; 9 Audiocassette(s) (Box 106)
    - Edge Public Lecture: Dr. Goheen, 1983; 1880; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Woodrow Wilson School, Paul Volcker Class of 1949, 1984; 1772; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - US/Japanese Trade Conference, 1984; 1787; 5 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - Socialism in US, 1984; 1852; 4 Audiocassette(s) (Box 111)
    - Software Industry?, 1984; 1945; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 114)
    - Art Museum, Emmet Gowin, 1984; 1925; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Divestiture Forum, 1985; AR.2001.063; 1290; 2 Videocassette(s) (Box 23-24)
      unedited raw footage. Created by Ground Floor Video. VHS.
    - Hubert N. Alyea - "Lucky Accidents, Great Discoveries and the Prepared Mind", 1985; AR.2001.063; 1296; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 24)
      Film about chemistry professor Hubert Alyea (1903-1996) with excerpts of his lecture "Lucky Accidents, Great Discoveries and the Prepared Mind." Alyea used it as guest lecturer all over the country after his retirement. This footage is from a recording at Louisiana State University. Alyea repeated the lecture for alumni each year. The film is produced by the Alumni Council. VHS; Duration: 27:28.
    - Hubert N. Alyea - "Lucky Accidents, Great Discoveries and the Prepared Mind", 1985; AR.2001.063; 1297; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 24)
      VHS; Duration: 27 min.
    - Forum on South Africa, 1985; 1741; 3 Audiocassette(s) (Box 108)
    - Secretary of State, George Shultz, 1985; 1744; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 108)
    - Causes of the Great Depression, Bernanke, 1985; 1745; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 108)
    - Professor Marvin Bressler, Guest Speaker, 1986 Senior Class Fall Dinner, 1985; 1824; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 203)
    - Professor Marvin Bressler, Guest Speaker, 1986 Senior Class Fall Dinner, 1985; 1824; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 110)
    - Public Lecture: Eudora Welty, 1985; 1877; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
      Sound Track from video. Compact cassette.
    - Conversation with Visual Arts Class, Eudora Welty, 1985; 1878; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Public Lecture: Professor Peter Russell, University of Toronto, 1985; 1891; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Public Lecture: Roy Romanow, 1985; 1893; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Public Lecture: J. Chretien, 1985; 1895; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Public Lecture: B. Dickson, 1985; 1897; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Donald H. Rumsfeld '54 - Alumni Day, 1985; AR.2008.151; 2018; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 194)
      Richardson Hall. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel; Duration: 55 min.
    - Ben Bernanke -- Fall Assembly, 1985; 2243; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - David Richardson Remarks, 1985; AR.2005.105; 2277; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 215)
    - Public Lecture: C. Ryan, circa 1985; 1889; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Mario Cuomo - McCosh 50, 1986; AR.2001.067; 1539; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 103)
    - President William Bowen: appointment of Ying-shih Yu (EAS); Roger S. Berlind '52 Distinguished Lectureship in Creative Writing to Joyce Carol Oates; Princeton Scholars Program; establishment of PRINCO (Princeton Investment Company), 1986; AR.2001.067; 1550; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 103)
    - Global Logistic Symposium, 1986; 1627; 13"Audiocassette(s) (Box 57)
    - Woodrow Wilson School Martin Feldstein, 1986; 1664; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 106)
    - R. W. Lee Memorial Symposium, 1986; 1692; 3 Audiocassette(s) (Box 106)
    - Woodrow Wilson School, Lord Roll, 1986; 1749; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 108)
    - Mario Cuomo, 1986; 1752; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 108)
    - Woodrow Wilson School, Robert Goheen, William Bundy, 1986; 1758; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 108)
    - Woodrow Wilson School, Califano, 1986; 1760; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 108)
    - Woodrow Wilson School, Kenneth Adelman, 1986; 1762; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 108)
    - Woodrow Wilson School, Richard Page, 1986; 1763; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 108)
    - Alumni Faculty, Panel, "Reflections on Teaching at Princeton", 1986; 1843; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 111)
    - Alumni Faculty Forum, "Ancient Greek Olympic Festival", 1986; 1844; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 111)
    - Alumni Faculty Forum, "Princeton Update", 1986; 1845; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 111)
    - Alumni Faculty Forum, "?", 1986; 1846; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 111)
    - Public Lecture: Ross S. Stein, 1986; 1903; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "The Black Death and Other Plagues" Robert S. Gottfried, 1986; 1904; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "Building Failures and Creativity in Architectural Design" Slobodan Curcic, 1986; 1905; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "Disease Epidemics: Predictable Catastrophes?" Roy M Anderson, 1986; 1906; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "Catastrophes in Human Affairs" William H. McNeill, 1986; 1907; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Panel: Reflections on Teaching at Princeton -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2215; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 211)
    - Panel: Doing Business Across the Rio Grande - Alumni College, 1986; 2216; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 211)
    - R. D. French: What Border? American Popular Culture in Quebec - Alumni College, 1986; 2217; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 211)
    - W. Robert Connor: The Ancient Greek Olympic Festival -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2218; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 211)
    - Panel: Spring Cleaning the Environment: Waste Not, Want Not -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2219; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 211)
    - Panel: University Education - Who Needs It? The Role of the University in American Life -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2220; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 211)
    - The Dawn of Art: Ice Age Paintings and Engravings of France -- Pam J. Crabtree - Alumni Council, 1986; 2221; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 211)
    - Elaine Showalter -- Alumni Day, 1986; 2223; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Panel: Professional Sports, Drugs, and Other Curve Balls -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2224; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Panel: New Directions for Investments -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2225; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Panel: Developing Countries and the Real American Stake -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2226; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - David Billington -- Alumni Day, 1986; 2227; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Alvin B. Kernan -- Alumni Day, 1986; 2229; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Carolyn Abbate -- Alumni Council, 1986; 2230; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Prof. Paul Starr Presentation, 1986; 2231; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - G. Gerstle: French-Canadian Immigration to New England -- Alumni College, 1986; 2232; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Paul Sigmund: Mexican-American Economic Relations -- Alumni College, 1986; 2233; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Michael Peterman: Is There a Canadian Literature? -- Alumni College, 1986; 2234; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - M. J. Jimenez: Mexican Immigration to the United States -- Alumni College, 1986; 2235; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - William Ruckelshaus -- Alumni Council, 1986; 2236; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - John B. Hughes: Latin-American Literature -- Alumni College, 1986; 2238; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Dean Girgus et al. -- Alumni Day, 1986; 2239; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Round Table on Energy and the Environment -- Alumni College, 1986; 2240; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Arnold Levine - Molecular Biology -- Alumni Council, 1986; 2241; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Panel: Doing Business Across the 49th Parallel -- Alumni College, 1986; 2242; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Panel: Shooting the Moon: America's Aim in Space -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2250; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Panel: The Politician as Celebrity -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2251; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Panel: U.S. Trade with the Pacific Basin: Wave of the Future? -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2252; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Gillett Griffin: Pre-Columbian Art of Mexico -- Alumni College, 1986; 2253; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - John Murray: Changing Canadian Attitudes Toward Free Trade and American Direct Investment -- Alumni College, 1986; 2254; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Panel - Fat City: Urban Planning that Works -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2256; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Thomas Shenk - Molecular Biology -- Alumni Council, 1986; 2257; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - David R. Coffin -- Alumni Day, 1986; 2258; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Panel: Performing Arts in the Electronic Age -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2259; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 215)
    - Robert C. Darnton -- Alumni Day, 1986; 2262; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 215)
    - Lee Silver - Molecular Biology -- Alumni Council, 1986; 2263; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 215)
    - Milton Babbitt -- Alumni Day, 1986; 2264; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 215)
    - R. Challener: Introduction to the College + Carol Hasson: Immigration, 1986; 2265; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 215)
    - Stanley Katz: The Canadian Charter of Rights and its Implications -- Alumni College, 1986; 2266; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 215)
    - Panel Discussion: Princeton Update -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1986; 2267; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 215)
    - Looking Toward the Summit: Professors Pipes (Harvard) and Cohen (Princeton) - Soviet-American Relations Forum (unedited, 1987; AR.2001.063; 1282; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 24)
      Tape 1 of 2 (2nd not found). Created by Princeton U. Media Services. VHS.
    - Looking Toward the Summit: Professors Pipes (Harvard) and Cohen (Princeton) - Soviet-American Relations Forum, 1987; AR.2001.067; 1404; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 30)
      Created by Blackwell Corporation for American Interests. VHS; Duration: 58 min 50 sec.
    - Tuition Seminar - spring 1987, AR.2001.067; 1546; 3 Audiocassette(s) (Box 103)
      morning, lunch session. Compact cassette.
    - "E"-Quad Panel, 1987; 1625; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 105)
    - Princeton Universtiy Democrats: Cesar Chavez, 1987; 1658; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 105)
    - Art and Archaeology Pre-Columbian Round Table, 1987; 1660; 4 Audiocassette(s) (Box 105-106)
    - Woodrow Wilson School: Leadership in the Modern Presidency, Round Table Discussion, 1987; 1668; 3 Audiocassette(s) (Box 106)
    - Woodrow Wilson School, Fulbright Anniversary, "Democracy in Developing Countries," Rajni Kothari, 1987; 1751; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 108)
    - Woodrow Wilson School, SDI Debate, Courter/Torricelli, 1987; 1753; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 108)
    - Woodrow Wilson School, "Our Children, Our Future: Restoring the American Tradition of Community," J. R. Biden, Jr., 1987; 1755; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 108)
    - Woodrow Wilson School, Leadership in the Modern Presidency, re: Roosevelt, Truman, Eisenhower, Kennedy, Johnson, Nixon, Ford, Carter, Reagan, 1987; 1764; 5 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - Council on New Jersey Affairs, 1987; 1775; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - Regional Land Conservation Symposium, 1987; 1777; 5 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - Woodrow Wilson School, Program for New Jersey Affairs, 1987; 1782; 3 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - Chapel, Dr. Hans Kung, 1987; 1785; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - Class Day, 1987; 1825; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 110)
    - Toni Morrison African-American Studies, 1987; 1831; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 110)
    - Public Lecture: "Krakatau 1883 - The Volcanic Eruption and its Effects" Tom Simlin, 1987; 1879; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Public Lecture: "Autopsies, Inquiries, and the 19th Century Narrations of Catastrophies" Thomas Laqueur, 1987; 1881; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Steve Jobs at Princeton University, 1987; 1882; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Public Lecture: "Rethinking Disasters: Human Troubles in a New Age" Kai Erikson, 1987; 1883; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Public Lecture: "Weather, Climate, and Catastrophes" Stephen B. Fels, 1987; 1885; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Public Lecture: "AIDS," Lawrence Altman, M.D., 1987; 1886; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Public Lecture: "Why Scientists Cheat and Does it Matter?" Nicholas Wade, 1987; 1888; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Public Lecture: "Deceit in Science: Do Scientists Care?" N. Feder, W. Stewart, 1987; 1899; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112-113)
    - Public Lecture: "The Roots of Professional Ethics" Daniel Callahan, 1987; 1901; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "Cultural Resistance and the Holocaust Experience", 1987; 1908; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "Apocalyptic Religion and Violent Ends: The Jonestown Catastrophy", 1987; 1909; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - "The Physiological Basis of Training for Sport" Melvin H. Williams, 1987; 1918; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Sports Nutrition: "Winning Diets - Fact or Fiction" Audrey Burkart, 1987; 1919; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Sports Nutrition: "Sports Nutrition Tips" Nancy Clark, 1987; 1920; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - "God Working All Things for Good, Romans 8:28" -- Rev. David Marshall, 1987; AR.2004.047; 2091; 1 Disc(s) (Box 207)
      Preached while Pastor of Grace Church, Ridgewood NJ. Compact disc.
    - Humanity and the Humanities - Panel -- Alumni Day, 1987; 2244; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
      with J. Billington. Compact cassette.
    - Research Frontiers at Princeton - J. Girgus and others -- Alumni Day, 1987; 2246; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - The Humanities - Why? -- Alumni Day, 1987; 2247; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
      with Goheen and others. Compact cassette.
    - The Special Program in the Humanities and Today's Undergraduate Opportunities -- Alumni Day, 1987; 2249; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 214)
    - Edmund Keeley -- Alumni Council, 1987; 2260; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 215)
    - Adm. W. J. Crowe, Jr.: America and her Military: The Once and Future Challenges of Defending a Democracy -- Alumni Council, 1987; 2261; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 215)
    - King and Queen of Sweden, 1988; AR.2001.063; 1294; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 24)
    - Paul Volcker press conference, 1988; AR.2001.067; 1541; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 103)
      2 copies. Created by Princeton University Media Services. Compact cassette.
    - Gauss Colloquium, Masterpieces: Canonizing The Literary, 1988; 1652; 6 Audiocassette(s) (Box 105)
      Victor Brombert, Barbara H. Smith, Glenn W. Most, Froma Zeitlin, John J. Winkler, Henry Louis Gates, Jr., Steven Marcus. Compact cassette.
    - Center for International Studies, Robert J. Lifton, 1988; 1769; 3 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - Public Lecture: "The Handling of Innocence in American Literature" Mary Gordon, 1988; 1902; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "Physicians' Responsibility in Epidemics", 1988; 1910; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "El Salvador, Nicaragua and the Ethics of Human Rights Reporting" Aryeh Neier, 1988; 1911; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "Violence, Deceit, and the Ethics of Survival" Sissela Bok, 1988; 1912; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "The Place of Deceit in Political Life" Bernard A. O. Williams, 1988; 1913; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "The Voyage In: Third World Intellectuals and Metropolitan Cultures", 1988; 1914; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "Is He Worth It, and How Do I Know? The Female Dilemna in Insect Courtship", 1988; 1915; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Public Lecture: "Public Ethics and Public Good" Archibald Cox, 1988; 1916; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 113)
    - Vusi Khanyile press conference, 1989; AR.2001.067; 1544; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 103)
      Created by Princeton University Media Services. Compact cassette.
    - "E"-Quad Panel - Dean of the College, 1989; 1626; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 105)
    - Panel: Engineers and the Entrepreneurial Spirit -- Alumni Faculty Forum, 1989; AR.2005.105; 2286; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 215)
    - Dr. Ruth Westheimer - McCosh 50, 1990; AR.2001.063; 1288; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 23)
      First 16 minutes of a talk by Dr. Ruth Westheimer about sexuality. (The recording stops because of malfunctioning of the video recorder.). VHS; Duration: 1:22:37.
    - Gender and Education - "Gender and Campus Architecture" - Helen Lefkowitz Horowitz (Smith College) and Paul V. Turner (Stanford University), 1990; AR.2001.067; 1459; 2 Videocassette(s) (Box 35, 37)
    - Gender and Education - "The History of Coeducation" - Carol Lasser (Oberlin College) and Barbara Miller Soloman (Harvard University), 1990; AR.2001.067; 1482; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 37)
    - Gender and Education - "Gender and Culture" - Hazel V. Carby (Yale University) and Katie King (Cornell University), 1990; AR.2001.067; 1483; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 37)
    - Gender and Education - "Gender and Technology" - Ursula M. Franklin (University of Toronto) and Caroline Whitbeck (M.I.T.), 1990; AR.2001.067; 1484; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 37)
    - Gender and Education - "The Gendered Voice in the Classroom" - Jane Roland Martin (University of Massachusetts), 1990; AR.2001.067; 1489; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 38)
    - Dean Fred Hargadon - Admissions 101, circa 1990; AR.2001.067; 1410; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 30)
      Video recording of a presentation for parents of prospective students by Fred Hargadon, dean of admission. VHS; Duration: 1:10:00.
    - Dean Fred Hargadon - Admissions 101, circa 1990; 1410; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 223)
      Video recording of a presentation for parents of prospective students by Fred Hargadon, dean of admission.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-2; Duration: 1:10:00.
    - Dean Fred Hargadon - Admissions 101, circa 1990; 1410; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 223)
      Video recording of a presentation for parents of prospective students by Fred Hargadon, dean of admission.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-4; Duration: 1:10:00.
    - Dean Fred Hargadon - Admissions 101, circa 1990; Digital Files: 1
      Item number: 1410. Video recording of a presentation for parents of prospective students by Fred Hargadon, dean of admission. Duration: 1:10:00.
    - David Wilkinson - "Bubbles: The Intriguing World of Surface Tension", 1991; AR.2001.063; 1280; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 2)
      Hi8 video cassette.
    - WPVI Channel 6 Philadelphia - Soviet Break-up Spot, 1991; AR.2001.063; 1332; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 27)
    - Making It II - motivational tape for young black Americans, 1991; AR.2001.067; 1424; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 32)
    - Post-Soviet Union policy -- James A. Baker III '52, Secretary of State, 1991; AR.2001.067; 1486; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 37)
      Talk by Secretary of State James A. Baker III '52 about American policy after the collapse of the Soviet Union (co-sponsored by the Woodrow Wilson School and the Class of 1993). VHS; Duration: 57:40.
    - Post-Soviet Union policy -- James A. Baker III '52, Secretary of State, 1991; 1486; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      Talk by Secretary of State James A. Baker III '52 about American policy after the collapse of the Soviet Union (co-sponsored by the Woodrow Wilson School and the Class of 1993). Created by Colorlab. MPEG-2; Duration: 57:40.
    - Post-Soviet Union policy -- James A. Baker III '52, Secretary of State, 1991; 1486; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      Talk by Secretary of State James A. Baker III '52 about American policy after the collapse of the Soviet Union (co-sponsored by the Woodrow Wilson School and the Class of 1993). Created by Colorlab. MPEG-4; Duration: 57:40.
    - Post-Soviet Union policy -- James A. Baker III '52, Secretary of State, 1991; Digital Files: 1
      Item number: 1486. Talk by Secretary of State James A. Baker III '52 about American policy after the collapse of the Soviet Union (co-sponsored by the Woodrow Wilson School and the Class of 1993)". Duration: 57:40.
    - "A Financial Primer", 1991; AR.2005.105; 2273; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 210)
    - "The Quality of Teaching at Princeton", 1991; AR.2005.105; 2292; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 216)
    - America: The Fires Within - debate on the Rodney King trial hosted by Charlie Rose - with Cornel West (Afro-American Studies) and Jonathan Rider (Institute for Advanced Study), 1992; AR.2001.067; 1425; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 32)
      Created by Advertising Information Services. VHS; Duration: 60 min.
    - Quantum: The Science Series - Professor David Wilkinson and cosmic background radiation, 1992; AR.2001.067; 1444; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 34)
      aired in Australia. Created by Australia Broadcasting Corporation. VHS.